Hey, guys.
얘들아
So, what do you think?
어떻게 생각해?
-About what?
-What?
- 뭐가?
- 뭐?
Are you kidding?
Okay, I'll give you a hint.
농담하는거야?
힌트 줄게
Eyes.
눈, 아니, 네 눈!
아니구
No, no. Your eyes! No.
Chandler's eyes!
챈들러 눈!
I got glasses.
안경 마련했어
You always had glasses.
항상 썼잖아
No, I didn't.
아니야
Are you sure?
확실해?
Didn't you have a pair?
쓰지 않았었나?
They were really round and burgundy,
and they made you look kind of...
자주색의 둥근 안경테에
어딘가 좀...
-Feminine.
-Yes!
- 여성스러웠지
- 맞아!
No.
아니야
I think the glasses look great.
You look sexy.
자기 멋있어
섹시해 보이는걸
-Really?
-Yeah.
- 정말?
- 그럼
You didn't think I wore glasses?
전에 안 썼다는 건 알지?
Of course.
그럼
The One With Phoebe's Cookies
What do you want for
an engagement gift?
약혼 선물로 원하는게 뭐야?
That's okay, we're not
having a party...
괜찮아, 파티도 안 하는데
so you don't have to get us..
그러니까 줄 필요...
If someone wants to give us a present,
we can't deprive them of that joy.
주고 싶다는데 왜
그 기쁨을 빼앗으려는 거야?
You should get them a
little CD player.
CD 플레이어 사줘라
I already have one.
벌써 있어
누가 산부인과에 갖고 갔다
잃어버렸다면 필요할 걸
Unless someone borrowed it and
left it at the gynecologist.
'누가'는 조이를 말하는거야
Yeah, and by "someone"
she means Joey.
원하는 것 있어
I know what I want!
- 우리가 원하는것?
- 아니, 자기 말구
-What we want, honey.
-No, you don't want this.
네 할머니의
쿠키 요리법을 알려줘
I want your grandmother's
cookie recipe.
초코칩 쿠키 말이야?
You mean the chocolate chip
cookie recipe?
할머니가 돌아가실 때
꼭 비밀로 하라고
The one my grandma
made me swear on her deathbed...
약속 받았던 그것 말이야?
that I would never
let out of our family?
사람들이 죽을 때
참 이상한 얘기들을 하지
Dying people say the craziest things.
쭉 알고 싶었어
애들에게 만들어 주고 싶어
I've wanted it for years. I was gonna
make cookies for my children.
가슴 아프게, 좋아
Break my heart. Oh, all right.
최고의 초코칩 쿠키를
만드는 엄마가 될거야
I'll be the mom who makes the
world's best chocolate chip cookies.
우리 아이들
뚱뚱하겠군
Our kids are gonna be fat,
aren't they?
안녕!
Ahoy!
- 배는 잘 있구?
- 항해에 맛들렸어
-How's the boat?
-I'm getting into this sailing stuff.
드디어 선착장에서 뺐구나
You finally took it out of the marina?
뭐하러?
Why would I do that?
3명이서 겨우 들여 놨는데
It took three guys
to get the thing in there.
안 타면 배에서 뭘하니?
If you don't sail it,
what do you do on it?
그냥 앉아서 쉬면서
It's a great place to just sit...
맥주 마시고 간식하기 딱 좋아
hang around, drink a few beers,
eat some chips.
쉴 수 있는 장소를
찾아서 잘 됐네
It's good that you finally
have a place to do that.
내가 배타는 법 가르쳐 줄게
I could teach you to sail if you want.
- 할 수 있어?
- 늘 해 왔는걸
-You could?
-I've been sailing my whole life.
15살때
아빠가 보트를 사줬거든
When I was 15, my dad
bought me my own boat.
- 보트를?
- 날 위로해 준다고
-Your own boat?
-He was trying to cheer me up.
내 조랑말이 아팠거든
My pony was sick.
'센트럴 퍼크'
- 내가 뭘 생각하는지 알아?
- 뭔데?
-You know what I was thinking?
-What?
아무 생각 없지
그냥 이러는게 좋아서
Nothing, I just like to go like this.
- 이따가 뭐해?
- 왜, 강의 있어?
-What are you doing tonight?
-Do you have a lecture?
- 아니, 왜 물어봐?
- 그럼... 난 한가해
-No, why?
-Then, free as a bird. What's up?
우리 아빠가 라켓볼 치자는데
My dad wants to know if you want
to play racquetball.
아빠가 자기를 좋아하나봐!
Great! Dad must like you!
아무하고나 안 치시거든
He doesn't ask just anyone to play.
네가 아니라
'챈시'라고 했어
He didn't ask for you.
He asked for "Chauncey."
너를 뜻하는 것 같아서
I assumed he meant you.
똑바로 알려 드렸어?
Did you correct him?
아니, 이게 더 재밌잖아
No, I thought it would be
more fun this way.
잘 됐네, 매주 치면 좋겠다
Cool! Maybe you could
do this every week.
아니면 앞마당에 앉아서
Or you could sit on the porch...
쓰레기통 지킬 수도 있구
and make sure no one
steals the trashcans.
그 일도 매주 하시거든
He does that every week too.
충고하겠는데 져 드려야 돼
지는 건 질색이시거든
Just so you know, you have to let
him win. He hates to lose.
왼손으로 치면 되겠다
Maybe I'll play with my left hand.
원래 왼손잡이 아냐?
You're not a lefty?
아무도 날 모르는군
Does anybody know me?
왜 그래?
What's wrong?
쿠키 요리법을 가지러
전에 살던 아파트에 갔더니
I went to my old apartment
to get the cookie recipe...
불에 타버렸지 뭐야!
and that stupid fire burned it up!
왜 복사해서 원본과
30미터 이상 떨어진
No! Why didn't you make a copy
and keep it in a fireproof box...
방화된 금고에 안 보관했어?
and keep it at least 100 yards
away from the original?
난 정상인이니까 그렇지
Because I'm normal.
할머니가 물려준 건
그것 뿐이었어
That was the one legacy
my grandmother left me.
넌 약혼 선물로
원했었구
And I know you wanted it
as an engagement present.
약혼 선물 주기로 했어?
We have to get you
an engagement present?
걱정마
Don't worry about it.
난 약혼 선물 받은 적 없는데
No one got me an engagement present.
요리법은 없지만 이것 받아
I don't have the recipe, but here.
건강과 행복을 기원한다
I wish you health
and happiness.
오래된 쿠키?
An old cookie?
선물 목록 안 만들면
이렇다니까
This is what happens when you
don't register for gifts.
전에 만들어서 얼려 둔 건데
이것만 남았어
I made a batch and froze it.
This is the only one left.
받을 수 없어
We can't accept this.
뭐 어때?
Why not?
지저분하니까
Cause it's gross.
잠깐만, 이 쿠키를 써서
요리법을 알 수 있을지 몰라
No, wait. I think I can figure out
the recipe from this cookie.
일할때 항상 하는거야
I do this at work all the time.
- 정말?
- 할 수 있어!
-Really?
-I think so!
그래, 약혼 선물 줄게
Okay, Ross, we owe you a present.
2개! 약혼 2번 했잖아
Two! I've been engaged twice.
이 녀석 좀 봐
Look at this clown.
큰 배라고 강을 다
휘젓고 다니잖아
He thinks he can take up the
whole river.
비켜, 이 멍청아!
Get out of the way, jackass!
무슨 배 이름이
'해안 경비대'야?
Who names their boat
Coast Guard, anyway?
해안 경비대 배니까
That is the Coast Guard.
여기서 뭐하는거야?
What are they doing here?
해안은 저쪽이잖아
The coast is all the way over there.
배들은 신경 꺼
Joey, just ignore the boats.
- 아직 다 안 끝났어
- 알았어
-We're not finished with our lesson.
-All right.
기본 요점들을
다시 한 번 말한다
I'm gonna go over the basic
points once more.
레이첼, 다 알겠다니까
Come on, Rach. I got it, okay?
저쪽에 저...
I want to go over there...
여자들이 잔뜩 탄
배쪽으로 가고 싶어
where that boatload of girls is.
그것뿐이야?
저쪽으로 가서
Is that it? You want to give...
멋진 여자들한테
말 걸고 싶은거야?
a shout to the hot chicas?
그렇게 하자, 조이 선원
Okay, let's do that, Sailor Joe.
그럼 물어보자
이걸 뭐라고 부르지?
Quick question, though:
What's this called?
- 배 끈?
- 틀렸어
-Boat rope?
-Wrong!
주범은 어떻게 올리지?
How do you get the mainsail up?
어루만져 주나?
Rub it?
아냐, '방향 전환'이라고
말하면 어떻게 해야 되지?
No. What do you do if I say
we're coming about?
'또 와요'라고 답하지
I say, "Come again?"
알아, 이건 아는데
I know this one. I know this one.
시간 초과, 넌 죽었어
Time's up. Now you're dead.
귀머거리에다가!
And deaf!
계속 농담 해 봐
You go on and make your little jokes.
제대로 못하면
If you don't know
what you're doing...
죽는 수가 있어
알아 듣겠어?
you will die.
Am I getting through to you?
- 네
- 대답만 하지마
-Yes.
-Don't just say yes.
장난이 아니야
크게 다칠 수가 있어
This isn't a game.
You could get hurt out here!
정신 차릴래 아니면 죽을래?
Do you want to pay attention,
or do you want to die?
챈들러한테 전화할래
I want to make a
ship-to-shore call to Chandler.
- 육두구 맛이 확실해
- 그래?
-I definitely taste nutmeg.
-You do?
넌 모르겠니? 그게 바로
You don't? Well, that's
the difference...
프로와 아마추어의 차이지
between a
professional and a layman.
잘난 척이기도 하고
That and arrogance.
야
Hey.
배타기는 어땠어?
Hey. How was sailing?
말하고 싶지 않아
I don't want to talk about it.
쿠키 하나 쯤은 남겨두지
You could've at least saved
me a cookie.
여자들은 못됐어!
Women are mean!
믿을 수가 없어
I can't believe that.
이제 할머니가
물려 주신 거라곤
Now the only thing left
of my grandmother's legacy is...
이 부스러기 뿐이네
this crumb.
오래 행복한 결혼 생활을 하길
I wish you a long and happy marriage.
- 야
- 어땠어?
-Hey.
-How was it?
난 엄청 재밌었어
Well, I had a great time.
챈시는 그렇지 못했지
Chauncey on the other hand...
내가 얘기 할께
I will tell the story.
좋았었어
시합에 져 드리고 친해져서
It was going great.
I let him win, we were bonding...
아버지라고 부르라셨어
he even said I could call him Dad.
뭐라고는 부르지 말라고?
And what did he ask you
not to call him?
자기
"Daddy."
이렇게 된 일이야
Look, here's the story.
라켓볼 마치고 다같이
증기욕실에 갔어
We had just finished playing,
and we were gonna take a steam.
들어가 보니까
I walk into the room...
증기가 심하더라구
and it's really steamy.
그래서 안경을 벗었고
그 일이 벌어졌지
So I take off my glasses,
and that's when it happened.
어디세요?
Guys?
- 이쪽이야
- 앉게
-Over here.
-Have a seat, son.
이보게!
Hey!
- 세상에, 믿을 수 없어
- 그렇지
-Oh, my God! I can't believe it.
-I know.
우리 아빠 무릎에 앉았다니
You gave my father a lap dance.
증기가 왜 그렇게 많은거야?
Why do they put
so much steam in there?
증기가 없다면 증기욕실이 아니라
그냥 욕실이 되니까
Because otherwise they'd
have to call it the "room" room.
왜?
왜 그런일이 있어야 했지?
Why?
Why did that have to happen?
별것도 아니네
Come on, it's not that big a deal.
별것도 아니라구?
Not that big a deal?
만지기도 했었다구
There was touching of things.
우리 아빠와
친해지고 싶었겠지만
I know you wanted
to bond with my dad...
꼭 그 부분과
친해야만 했냐?
but did you have to bond
to that part?
아빠는 상관 안 할거야
I'm sure Dad doesn't care.
우습다고 생각했을 걸
He probably thought it was funny.
두고두고 얘기 하실 걸
He'll be telling this story for years.
얘기 안 하시면 좋겠어
I don't want him to tell
this story for years.
그렇게는 안 될걸
Oh, but he will.
아직도 모니카의 체중감량 캠프
탈출 사건 얘기를 하잖아
He still tells the story about how
Monica tried to escape from fat camp.
탈출하려고 안 했어
I wasn't escaping.
그럼 가시 철사엔
왜 걸렸어?
Then how'd you get caught
in the barbed wire?
다람쥐를 풀어주려다 그랬어
I was trying to help out a squirrel.
먹으려고 했잖아
You were trying to eat it.
네 아빠가 그 얘기하려고
전화하는 거면
If that is your father calling
to tell this story...
우리 결혼 안 한다!
then the marriage is off!
그러지마
여보세요?
Come on. Hello.
미안, 잘못 거셨어요
I'm sorry, you have the wrong number.
이따 전화할게요, 아빠
사랑해요
I'll call you later, Dad.
I love you.
네 아버지 뵈러 간다
I'm off to see your dad.
옷을 너무 많이
입지 않았냐?
Aren't you a little overdressed?
이번엔 꼭 팁 챙겨라
You better make sure
he tips you this time.
더 이상 그 얘기
하지 마시라고 부탁 드리려구
I figured I would try to convince
him not to tell the story anymore...
직접 뵙고 말하는게
좋을 것 같아서
and I figured the best way
to do that was face to face.
직접 뵌다는 건
그 분 무릎과
And by "face," I don't mean his lap.
내 엉덩이 얘기가 아니야
And by "face," I don't mean my ass.
모니카와 챈들러한테
약혼 선물 사줄거야?
Are you getting Monica and
Chandler a present?
모르겠어
우리는 안 받았잖아
I don't know. You know,
they didn't get us anything.
내 말이 그 말이야!
Thank you!
야
Hey.
안녕
Well, hello.
또 언제 바다로 나갈까, 친구?
So when are we getting
back out on the water, matey?
뱃사람 말로는 못하겠지만
절대로 안 가!
I don't know the boat way
to say this, but, never.
왜?
Why not?
배타면 넌 참 못됐어
Because you're mean on the boat.
가르쳐 주려는 것 뿐이야
I was just trying to teach you.
배울 것 다 배웠어
'레이첼은 못됐다'
Well, lesson learned.
Rachel is mean.
맞아, 맞아
Yep, yep, yep.
레이첼이 자기 아빠 배에
태워 줬을때
I remember when she took me out
on her dad's boat.
절대로 못 돕게 하더라구
She wouldn't let me help at all.
도움을 원했지만
Excuse me, I wanted you to help.
네가 움직일 수 없었잖아
But you couldn't move...
구명 재킷을 3개나 입었으니까
because you were wearing
three life jackets.
바다를 두려워
할 줄 알아야 돼
You have to respect the sea.
못돼게 했다면 미안해
Joey, I'm sorry if you thought
that was mean.
하지만 그건 아무것도 아니야
But I tell you, that was not mean.
우리 아빠가 못됐지
배만 탔다하면 소리를 질렀거든
My father is mean. He used to always
yell at me on the boat.
끔찍했어
난 좋은 스승 노릇만 한거야
It was horrible.
I was being a really good teacher.
좋은 스승이 '맥주 그만
마셔, 멍청아' 그래?
Does a good teacher say,
"Put down the beer, pinhead!"
착한 학생이 첫 수업에
맥주를 7캔이나 마셔?
Does a good student drink 7 beers
during his first lesson?
6개 반이야
Six and a half.
마지막 건 네가 쳐버렸잖아
You knocked the last
one out of my hand, remember?
방재에 맞을까봐 그랬어
I didn't want you to get hit
by the boom.
그래도 맞았어
Well, it hit me anyway.
마지막 캔을 다 마셨더라면
덜 아팠을거라구
It would have hurt a lot less
if I had finished that last beer.
미안해
언성 그만 높일게
I'm sorry. I will try to tone it down
and stop yelling.
이래라 저래라 안 할 거지?
No bossing me around?
- 알았어
- 친절할거지?
-I won't boss you around.
-And be nice?
- 그럴게
- 셔츠도 벗을거구?
-I'll be nice.
-You'll be topless?
- 조이!
- 내가 배우길 원한다며?
-Joey!
-You want me to learn?
22번이야
네 할머니 것 같을 지 몰라
Here's batch 22.
Maybe these are like your grandma's.
오렌지 껍질 좀 넣고
육두구는 없어
This has a bit of orange peel,
but no nutmeg.
먹어 보자
Let's give it a shot.
이렇게 많이 만든 건
중 3때가 마지막이야
I haven't made so many cookies
since 9th grade.
만들어 팔려고?
What for, a bake sale?
아니, 그냥 금요일 밤이라서
No, just a Friday night.
맛 좋은데
These are pretty good.
그런데 17번보단 못해
Yeah, but not as good as batch 17.
어떤 거였지?
Which one was that?
오빠가 거의 토할 뻔
한 뒤에 먹었던 것
The ones we had after
you almost threw up.
맞아, 17번이 맛있었어
Oh, yeah, batch 17 was good.
16번은 틀렸어
I did not like batch 16.
괜찮아
I'm okay.
17번에서 남은 것 있어?
그걸로 연구해 보면 되잖아
Any more from the good batch?
We could work off those.
하나 남았을 걸
I think there's one left.
16번이야
16번이라구! 비켜!
Batch 16.
Sixteen, people, get out of the way!
조이, 아주 잘하고 있어
Okay, Joey. You're doing really good.
좌현으로 가 봐
I just need you
to step to the portside.
좌현에 관한 얘기 기억나지?
Remember talking about the portside?
그럼
Oh, yeah.
아니
No.
왼쪽을 말하는거야
괜찮아, 어려운 거였어
It's left, sweetie, but that's okay.
That's a tough one.
그냥 왼쪽이라고 하면 안 돼?
Why not just say left?
그래 왼쪽으로 가
Okay, go to the left.
왼쪽
The left.
그냥 저리 앉아!
Just sit over there!
또 소리 지르잖아
You're yelling again. See that?
아니, 조용히
사랑으로 말하는 거야
Oh, no, no. Very quiet.
Said with love, no yelling.
You know what?
기왕 왔으니까
좌현에서 맥주나 마셔야지
Since I'm here, I'm gonna have
a beer on the portside.
잘 활용했지?
See what I did there?
좀 러핑하는데
커닝햄을 조여줄래?
We're luffing a little.
Can you tighten up the Cunningham?
지금 내가 모르는
말들을 잔뜩 했어
You just said a bunch
of stuff I don't know.
조이!
방금 배운 거잖아!
Joey, come on!
We just went over this.
그 땐 새를 쳐다봤었어
We did that when that bird...
물고기를 입에 물었는데
flew over with the fish
in his mouth.
봤어? 징그러웠어
Did you see it? It was gross.
새고 물고기고 못 봤어!
I did not see the bird or the fish!
타이슨처럼 생긴
스티로폼 조각도 못봤어!
I did not see the piece of
Styrofoam shaped like Mike Tyson!
네게 배타는 법을
가르쳐 주느라 못 봤어
I did not, because I was trying
to teach you how to sail a boat.
보시다시피
불가능한 일이지만
Which obviously is
an impossible thing to do.
또 소리 지르네
셔츠도 안 벗었구
You're yelling, and I don't
see you taking your top off.
그만 둘래!
I quit!
- 무슨 소리야? 포기 못해!
- 왜?
-What do you mean? You can't quit.
-Why not?
안 끝났어!
그린들은 포기 안 해!
You're not finished! I won't have it.
Greenes do not quit.
그린?
Greenes?
난 트리비아니라구
트리비아니들은 포기해
I'm a Tribbiani. Tribbianis quit.
세상에나
Oh, my God.
내가 방금
'그린들은 포기 안 해' 그랬지?
I just said, "Greenes don't quit,"
didn't I?
'그린들은 포기 안 해'
했지!
Did I say, "Greenes don't quit"?
그랬어! 아직도 소리 지르네
Yes! And you're still yelling at me.
아니, 너한테 지르는 거 아냐
네 옆에서 지르는거야
No, I'm not yelling at you.
I'm just yelling near you.
나 꼭 우리 아빠 같잖아
Oh, God, Joey. I'm my father.
어머, 끔찍해
Oh, my God. This is horrible.
엄마처럼 안 되려 애쓰다 보니
이쪽은 생각도 못했네
I try so hard not to be my mother,
I didn't see this coming.
정말 미안해
네가 배우길 원했어
I'm so sorry.
I just wanted you to learn.
배웠어
I did learn.
- 진심이야?
- 그렇다니까
-Really?
-Yeah, come on.
괜찮아
It's okay.
주범이 뭔지 안다구
I know what a mainsail is.
방재가 지날땐 피할 줄도 알구
I know to duck when
the boom comes across.
- 좌현은 오른쪽이란 것도
- 왼쪽
-I know port is right.
-Left.
제기랄!
Damn it!
우리가 요리법을
알아내려는 것을 아시면
It would make my grandmother happy...
할머니가 좋아 하실거야
that we're trying
to figure out her recipe.
밑에서 우리를 보시면서
아마 미소짓고 계실거야
I bet she's looking up at us
and smiling right now.
밑에서?
Looking up?
나한텐 잘 해주셨지만
확실히 지옥에 계실거야
She was really nice to me but
she's in hell for sure.
할 건 다 해 봤어
Well, I've tried everything.
포기할래
최고의 쿠키를
I give up.
I'm not gonna be the mom...
만드는 엄마가 못 되겠지
who makes the world's
best cookies.
최고의 오리와 브로콜리
요리는 할 수 있어
I do make the best
duck confit with broccoli raab.
그런 거 애들이 좋아하지?
Kids love that, right?
요리법을 가지고 있는
친척 없을까?
Isn't there any relative
that has the recipe?
네 쌍둥이 언니는?
What about your sister?
내 자신과 약속했어
다음에 우르술라와
No. I made a promise to
myself that the next time...
얘기를 나눌 날은
내가 죽는 날이라구
I would talk to Ursula
is over my dead body.
그날은 2032년
10월 15일이 될 거야
And that's not happening
till October 15, 2032.
너 그날 죽을 거야?
That's the day you're gonna die?
난 그날 약속 있는데
I've got shuffleboard that day.
그건 네 생각이지
That's what you think.
할머니 친구분 중에
아는 분 안 계실까?
What about friends of your grandma?
Wouldn't they have the recipe?
프랑스에 있는 친척 중
누가 알지도 몰라
I may have relatives in France
who would know.
우리 할머니는 자기 할머니
'네스리 툴라우스'한테 받은거래
My grandmother said she got it from
her grandmother, "Nestley Toulouse."
이름이 뭐라구?
What was her name?
네스리 툴라우스
Nestley Toulouse.
네슬리 톨하우스 말이야?
Nestle Tollhouse?
미국인들은 항상
프랑스어가 엉망이라니까
You Americans always butcher
the French language.
피비, 요리법이 이거야?
Phoebe, is this the recipe?
맞아!
Yes!
어머나
Oh.
믿을 수가 없어
I cannot believe that I spent...
이틀 동안 헛고생 한거야
two days figuring out that recipe.
바로 코 앞에 있었는데
It was here the whole time!
그러게 말이야
바로 이런 일 때문에
I know! You see,
it is stuff like this...
지옥에서 썩고 계신다구요!
which is why
you're burning in hell!
그래서 말이죠
So you understand.
사람들한테 얘기
안 하셨으면 해요
I'd feel better if you
didn't tell what happened.
좀 쑥스럽거든요
I'm a little embarrassed about it.
이해하지
I understand completely.
장인장모 앞에서 실수하는
것만큼 창피한 게 있나
Nothing's scarier
than embarrassing yourself...
in front of your in-laws.
자네 장모를 처음 사귈땐
실업자였는데
As a matter of fact, when I started
dating Judy, I was unemployed.
장인어른이
내 직업을 묻더라구
Her father asked me
what I did for a living.
변호사라고 거짓말했어
I said I was a lawyer.
- 알았을 땐 어땠어요?
- 아직도 모르셔
-What'd you do when they found out?
-They never did.
그러니까 내가 법률용어를
주절대도 모르는 척 해
So if you ever see me giving them
legal advice, just nod along.
들어가세
Shall we?
수영복을 입어야
되는 곳이군요
So, I guess we wear swimsuits in here.
인정하고 싶진 않지만
Well, Joey, I hate to admit it...
네 방식으로 배타는게
훨씬 재밌다
your way of sailing
is a lot more fun.
저 끈 잡아당겨 봐
Why don't you give a pull
on that rope?
항해 중도 아닌데
We're not sailing.
- 당겨보라니까
- 그러지
-Just pull on it.
-All right.
샌드위치네!
Sandwiches!
당연하지!
What else?
받아
Here you go.
- 고마워
- 이야
-Thank you.
-Oh, wow.
- 뭐하는거야?
- 미안해
-What are you doing?
-Sorry.
그렇게 잡지마
안에 것이 삐져 나오잖아
Not like that. You're letting
all the good stuff fall out.
조심해!
아까운 햄을!
Careful!
You're wasting good pastrami!
으악, 나 아버지랑 똑같잖아..
Oh, my God. I'm my dad!